const Question = {
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is pair programming?",
      correct: "blue",
      blue:
        "Blue: Pair programming is an agile software development technique in which two programmers work together at one workstation. One, the driver, writes code while the other, the observer or navigator, reviews each line of code as it is typed in. The two programmers switch roles frequently.",
      red: "Red: One person naps while the other person does all the work.",
      yellow: "Yellow: Two people get paid to chat about Star Wars.",
      orange:
        "Orange: Two people are put into a closed space and the senior developer is allowed to use brass knuckles on the junior developer until a reasonable solution is brought forth.",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What is Imposter Syndrome?",
      correct: "orange",
      blue: "Blue: Trump's Raison d'Ãªtre",
      red: "Red: A necessecity for folks in the witness protection program.",
      yellow: "Yellow: A constant need to act on Broadway.",
      orange:
        "Orange: A feeling that you are not qualified to hold the position for which you were hired.",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Who was named a 'Notable Entrepreneur' by Crain's Chicago?",
      correct: "yellow",
      blue: "Blue: Matt DuBois",
      red: "Red: Shamyle Ghazali",
      yellow: "Yellow: JC Grubbs",
      orange: "Orange: Mina Slater",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Who works in Engineering for Tandem?",
      correct: "yellow",
      blue: "Blue: Woody Woodpecker",
      red: "Red: Elizabeth Coleman",
      yellow: "Yellow: Sasha Grodzins",
      orange: "Orange: Kim Jong-Un",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Where did JC Grubbs attend undergraduate studies?",
      correct: "red",
      blue: "Blue: MIT",
      red: "Red: Campbell University",
      yellow: "Yellow: University of Louisville",
      orange: "Orange: University of Kentucky",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What did JC Grubbs study during his undergraduate years?",
      correct: "orange",
      blue: "Blue: Philosophy",
      red: "Red: Yoga",
      yellow: "Yellow: Basket-weaving",
      orange: "Orange: Classical Piano",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What was Tandem known by before it was Tandem?",
      correct: "red",
      blue: "Blue: Tonedeaf",
      red: "Red: DevMynd",
      yellow: "Yellow: GarageLogic",
      orange: "Orange: ByteMe",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Fill in the Blanks - LGBTQ + _ + _?",
      correct: "red",
      blue: "Blue: What?",
      red: "Red: I (Intersex); + A (Asexual) +",
      yellow: "Yellow: Now I know my ABC's",
      orange: "Orange: Social Empathy",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question:
        "Trump's mouth could be mistaken for Chicago because it is very___?",
      correct: "yellow",
      blue: "Blue: Orange-stained with cheetoh dust.",
      red: "Red: Gaping as the Chicago Spire.",
      yellow: "Yellow: Windy.",
      orange: "Orange: Open.",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question:
        "Who was recognized by Clutch.co as one of the top software development firms in the nation on multiple occasions.?",
      correct: "red",
      blue: "Blue: Grandma Miles",
      red: "Red: Tandem",
      yellow: "Yellow: Interapt",
      orange: "Orange: TechNode",
    },
  ],
};

export default Question;
